{
    "english": [
      {
        "question": "jabłko",
        "answer": "an apple"
      },
      {
        "question": "chleb",
        "answer": "bread"
      },
      {
        "question": "pies",
        "answer": "a dog"
      },
      {
        "question": "otrzymać",
        "answer": "to receive"
      },
      {
        "question": "nakładać makijaż",
        "answer": "put your face on"
      },
      {
        "question": "przymierzać",
        "answer": "try sth on"
      },
      {
        "question": "pora roku",
        "answer": "season"
      },
      {
        "question": "otrzymać",
        "answer": "to receive"
      },
      {
        "question": "meduza",
        "answer": "jellyfish"
      },
      {
        "question": "zajęty",
        "answer": "busy"
      },
      {
        "question": "zmęczony",
        "answer": "tired"
      },
      {
        "question": "wczoraj",
        "answer": "yesterday"
      },
      {
        "question": "zrezygnować z pracy",
        "answer": "resign a job"
      }
    ]
  }
